Cooker shows always against one person with an accent
电磁炉始终显示带有重音的人
Peel and cube
果皮和立方体
Ok so we need a pillow over here
好，所以我们需要一个枕头
Weather
天气
Note that
注意
This isn't working
这不行
How far something out really well
到底有多好
I cut myself
我切到了自己
Add a slight incident so cubing the potato
再加上一点点事件，这样就可以把马铃薯切块了
What's the name you just like butter
你像黄油一样叫什么名字
Replace the cube
更换立方体
You want YouTube stuff like the round
您想要YouTube之类的东西
Picasso would be proud of course
毕加索当然会为之骄傲
Tube in Peel this I'm gonna use this potato peeler to peel away
我要用这个土豆削皮器去皮
So I don't cut myself
所以我不会割伤自己
Hold your fingers make her like you
握住手指让她喜欢你
Knuckleball
旋转球
I remember doing this myself
我记得自己做过
Like surgery
喜欢切东西
And took you soon as possible
并尽快带你
Get yourself a flat surface
使自己平坦
Download like this
像这样下载
I don't like the turning in movie
我不喜欢看电影
My name is perfect
我的名字很完美
You want to get things as closest to a consistent size which sadly to say this is not
您想让东西最接近一致的大小，可悲的是，这不是
When is perfect cube potatoes Romania net worth
什么时候是完美的立方体土豆罗马尼亚净值
Does your playlist
你的播放清单
Sewing appeal in Cuba potato here to fill this potato
在古巴缝制土豆以填充这种马铃薯的吸引力
This is pretty straightforward
这很简单
What we looking to do is make perfect and even
我们要做的就是做到完美甚至
Tubes out of the potato
管出土豆
In order to get perfect cubes or we can have to do is have some fun
为了获得完美的立方体或我们所要做的就是找点乐子
Please guys can become mashed potatoes
伙计们可以变成土豆泥
Any number of operations the first thing I want to do is even up the shape
任何数量的操作我想做的第一件事就是使形状均匀
Get rid of birds from here
从这里摆脱鸟类
To come across and we're going to cut this into
遇到，我们将其切成
Planks planks into rectangles
木板成矩形
I'm going to come back across the other direction and we're going to cut these
我将回到另一个方向，我们将削减这些
One more
多一个
This is a bunch of matching
这是一堆匹配
All done I think they're close enough
我认为他们已经足够接近了
It's potatoes
是土豆